♫ Where do we go from here? ♫
♫إلى أين سنذهب ♫
♫ How do we carry on? ♫
♫مالذي سنأخذه معنا♫
♫ I can't get beyond the questions ♫
♫لا أستطيع أن أُهمل هذه الاسئلة♫
♫ Clambering for the scraps ♫
♫وأنا أجمع هذه القصاصات ♫
♫ in the shatter of us, collapsed ♫
♫ لقد تحطم الملجأ الذي كنا نحتمي به ♫
♫ It cuts me with every could have been ♫
♫ لقد جرحني في كل مكان ♫
♫ Pain on pain on play, repeating ♫
♫ألم و ألم يتكرر كلما أعزف ♫
♫ With the backup, makeshift life in waiting ♫
♫ سأنتظر حتى تتغير حياتي .. بعد أن أستعيدها♫
♫ Everybody says ♫
♫يقول الجميع ♫
♫ time heals everything ♫
♫أن الزمن يُشفي كل شيء♫
♫ What of the wretched hollow? ♫
♫ماذا عن البؤس الأجوف♫
♫ The endless in between? ♫
♫ماذا عن الوقوف في المنتصف الذي لاينتهي ♫
♫ Are we just going to wait it out? ♫
♫ هل سنبقى ننتظرها هكذا حتى تُفرج ♫
♫ There is nothing to see here now ♫
♫لا يوجد شيء يمكن ان نراه هنا ♫
♫ Turning the sign around ♫
♫أشعل هذه الأغنية ♫
♫ We're closed to the Earth 'til further notice ♫
♫فنحن أقرب ما يكون إلى الارض حسب علمي ♫
♫ A crumbling cliche case ♫
♫وضع مبتذل متعثر ♫
♫ crumpled and puffy faced ♫
♫ووجوه منتفخة وهائمة ♫
♫ caught dead in the stare of a thousand miles ♫
♫ وجدت ميتة تنظر إلى الأفق ♫
♫ All I want, only one street level miracle ♫
♫كل ما اريده هو طريق واحد للمعجزات ♫
♫ I'll be an out and out born again ♫
♫يحررني و أولد من جديد ♫
♫ from none more cynical ♫
♫ومن الآن سأسخر أكثر مما جرى ♫
♫ Everybody says ♫
♫يقول الجميع ♫
♫ that time heals everything ♫
♫أن الزمن يُشفي كل شيء♫
♫ But what of the wretched hollow? ♫
♫ماذا عن البؤس الأجوف♫
♫ The endless in between? ♫
♫ماذا عن الوقوف في المنتصف الذي لاينتهي ♫
♫ Are we just going to wait it out? ♫
♫ هل سنبقى ننتظرها هكذا حتى تُفرج ♫
♫ And sit here cold? ♫
♫هل سنبقى هنا في البرد ؟♫
♫ We will be long gone by then ♫
♫سنكون قد مُتنا حينها ♫
♫ In lackluster ♫
♫ بكل بهتان ♫
♫ In dust we lay around old magazines ♫
♫ نتمدد في التراب وحولنا المجلات القديمة ♫
♫ Fluorescent lighting sets the scene ♫
♫واضواء فوسفورية تنير المكان ♫
♫ for all we could and should be being ♫
♫من اجل كل مايمكن ان نكون ويجب ان نكون♫
♫ in the one life that we've got ♫
♫في هذه الحياة التي نعيش مرة واحدة ♫
♫ Everybody says ♫
♫يقول الجميع ♫
♫ time heals everything ♫
♫أن الزمن يُشفي كل شيء♫
♫ And what of the wretched hollow? ♫
♫ماذا عن البؤس الأجوف♫
♫ The endless in between? ♫
♫ماذا عن الوقوف في المنتصف الذي لاينتهي ♫
♫ Are we just going to wait it out? ♫
♫ هل سنبقى ننتظرها هكذا حتى تُفرج ♫
♫ Just going to sweat it out? ♫
♫هل سنتعفن هنا ونحن ننتظر ؟♫
♫ Wait it out ♫
♫ننتظر حتى تُفرج ♫
(Applause)
(تصفيق )